Guide to the Records of the Bureau of Public Occasions RG.4.2
New York University Archives
- Series I: General Files, 1935-1976; 1950-1975; 33 boxes
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1946 June 12 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1947 June 11 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1948 June 9 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1949 June 15 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1950 June 14 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1951 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1952 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1953 June 10 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1954 June 9 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1955 June 15 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1956 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1965 June 9 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Commerce, School of, Address to Alumni, Class of 1915, 1963 October 31 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Commerce, School of, Alumni Dinner, 1961 May 10 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Commerce, School of, Alumni Dinner, 1962 May 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Commerce, School of, Alumni Dinner, 1963 May 8 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Commerce, School of, Coffee Hour, 1964 March 11 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Convocation, 1956 September 27 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Council Meeting, 1950 May 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Courant, Professor Richard, Convocation honoring, 1958 January 8 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Courant, Lecture, Fifth, 1975 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Dean's Convocation, 1970 September 16 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Dean's Convocation for Students, 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Deems, Charles F., Lecture Series, 1962 March 28, April 4, 11 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Deems, Charles F., Lecture Series, 1963 March 6, 13, 20 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Deems, Charles F., Lecture Series, 1964 October 21, 28, November 4 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Deems, Charles F., Lecture Series, 1966 March 3, 10, 17 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Deems, Charles F., Lecture Series, 1967 March 8, 15, 22 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Deems, Charles F., Lecture Series, 1968 October 22, 29, November 12 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Deems, Charles F., Lecture Series, 1975 October 14-16 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Dentistry, College of, Alumni Association, Annual Awards Dinner, 1964 November 4 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Dentistry, College of, Alumni Association, Dean's Day, 1962 April 6 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Dentistry, College of, Alumni Association, Dinner, 1962 November 29 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dentistry, College of, Century Club, Annual Dinner, 1963, October 18 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Dentistry, College of, Commencement Exercises, 1975 February 24 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Dentistry, College of, Commencement Exercises, 1975 August 11 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Dori, General Yaacov (President of Technion-Israel Institute of Technology), Luncheon honoring, 1957 December 11 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dori, General Yaacov, Reception for, 1963 May 7 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Dovbrovina, Ludmila, Luncheon for, 1956 March 21 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Duke, James B.,House, Dedication of (Institute of Fine Arts), 1959 February 9 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Edison, Thomas A., Hall of Fame Installation, 1961 June 4 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Edison Foundation Institute, 1959 November 19 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Education Associates, Reception and Seminar, 1975 September 16 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Education, School of, Alumni Association, Conference, 1963 March 30 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Education, School of, Careers in Social Work, 1962 June 21 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Education, School of, Conference, 1960 April 2 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Education, School of, Conference-American Association of School Administrators, 1962 February 19 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Education, School of, Graduate Students Organization, 1962 January 12 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Education, School of, Workshop on University and College Administration, 1963 June 7 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Eisner, Joseph and Lubin, Joseph I., Auditorium, Dedication of (Loeb Student Center), 1959 December 5 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Engineering, College of, Centennial, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, College of, Convocation, 1955 May 7 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Engineering and Science, School of, Presidential Convocation for freshmen, 1964 September 19 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Engineering and Science, School of, Evening Division of, Class Day Exercises, 1964 July 9 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Medicine Research Center, Dedication of (Sterling Forest, New York), 1964 May 13 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Convocation, 1955 September 29 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Convocation, 1957 October 17 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Convocation, 1958 September 30 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Convocation, 1959 September 29 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Convocation, 1960 October 3 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Convocation, 1961 October 23 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Convocation-none held. (File contains correspondence concerning possibility of convocation), 1962 November (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Convocation, 1964 November 29 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Tea, 1953 October 25 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Tea, 1954 October 31 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Tea, 1955 October 23 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Tea, 1956 October 14 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Tea, 1957 October 6 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Tea, 1958 October 5 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Tea, 1959 October 11 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Tea, 1960 October 16 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Tea, 1961 November 12 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Tea, 1963 May 5 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Tea, 1963 November 13 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Women's Club of NYU, Luncheon, 1962 October 18 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Fales Collection, Opening of, 1963 October 24 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Fine Arts, Institute of, and National Endowment for the Humanities, Reception, 1973 November 7 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Students Reception, 1955 October 24 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Students Reception, 1956 October 24 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1956 April 27 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation and Newsom, Carroll Vincent, Inauguration, Folder #1, 1957 April 12 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation and Newsom, Carroll Vincent, Inauguration, Folder #2, 1957 April 12 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1958 April 18 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1959 April 17 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1960 April 22 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1961 April 21 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1962 April 27 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1963 April 19 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1964 April 23 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1965 April 29 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1966 April 21 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1969 April 17 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1970 April 16 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1971 April 22 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1972 April 27 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1973 April 26 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1974 April 25 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1975 April 24 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1976 April 22 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Fox, Levi, University Medal awarded to, 1964 June 25 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Freshmen Convocation, 1957 January 30 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Freshmen Convocation, 1957 September 16 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Freshmen Convocation, 1957 September 24 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Freshmen Convocation, 1959 September 21 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Freshmen Convocation, 1961 September 18-19 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Freshmen Convocation, 1962 February 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1950-1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1957 June 26 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1958 September 22-23 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Gabriel, Lady Mabel M., Honorary Degree awarded to, 1964 May 5 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1956 October 15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1957 November 12 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1959 January 28 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1959 November 10 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1960 November 22 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1961 November 8 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1962 April 17 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1962 November 7 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1963 November 12 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1963 October 14 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - General Education and Extension Services, Division of, Center for Safety Education, 25th Anniversary, Luncheon, 1964 May 26 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - General Education and Extension Services, Division of, Charitable Foundations Conference, 1965 May 10-11 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - General Education and Extension Services, Division of, Conference on Education for Creativity in the Sciences, 1963 June 13-15 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - General Education and Extension Services, Division of, Faculty Meeting, 1963 October 26 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Gibbs, Josiah Willard, Hall of Fame installation, 1957 December 1 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Goldman Band Concerts, 1975 June 18 - August 10 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Goodhart, Professor Arthur, Honorary Degree awarded to, 1955 June 24 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Gould, Frank Jay, Hall of Technology, Groundbreaking for, 1958 November 7 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Gould, Frank Jay, Hall of Technology, Cornerstone Ceremony, 1960 May 31 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Gould Student Center, Dedication of, 1954 October 30 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Students, Reception for, 1962 October 31 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Students Organization, Lecture, 1957 May 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Grey Art Gallery and Study Center, Dinner and Dedication, 1975 April 9 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Hauge, Gabriel, Luncheon in honor of, (Nichols Award presented to), 1975 May 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Hall, Sir Noel F., Lecture, 1958 February 6 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Hall of Fame Dinner, 1960 October 27 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Hayden Hall Dedication Ceremonies, 1957 April 5 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Heald, Chancellor Henry T., Dinner in honor of, 1952 February 7 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Heald, Chancellor Henry T.,Installation of and Commencement Exercises: Folder #1, 1952 June 11 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Heald, Chancellor Henry T., Installation of and Commencement Exercises: Folder #2, 1952 June 11 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Heald, Chancellor Henry T., and Newsom, President Carroll Vincent, Portraits of, Presentation, 1962 November 26 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Heiss, Carol, Parade, 1960 May 4 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Hernandez, German Zea (Ambassador of Columbia), Presidential Citation awarded to, 1963 December 13 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Hester, President James M., Dinner in Honor of, 1972 January 17 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Correspondence-General (1961 November - 1962 July), 1962 October 25 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Correspondence-General (1962 August - 1963 August), 1962 October 25 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Correspondence - Congratulations (1962-1963), 1962 October 25 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Address Suggestions (1962 August - 1962 October), 1962 October 25 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Clipping File, 1962 October 25 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Inaugural Address-Final Copies, 1962 October 25 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Inaugural Address-Rough drafts, 1962 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Guests, 1962 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Mailing lists-Folder #1, 1962 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Mailing lists-Folder #2, 1962 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Mailing lists-Folder #3, 1962 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Other material, 1962 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Press releases, 1962 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Printed material, 1962 October 25 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Printed material-proofs, 1962 October 25 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Preparations and Procedures - Releases, 1962 October 25 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Press Kit (Official), 1962 October 25 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hester, President James M., Inauguration of: Thank you letters, 1962 October 25 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Hester, President James M., Senate Reception for, 1962 February 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Higher Education, Conference on the Future in, (NYU Self-Study Program): Folder #1, 1956 September 27 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Higher Education, Conference on the Future in, (NYU Self-Study Program): Folder #2, 1956 September 27 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Himsworth, Sir Harold, University Medal awarded to, 1958 September 19 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Honeyman, Dr. T. J., Luncheon, 1955 November 30 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Honorary Society, 1962 April 12 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Indian Educators, Tea for, 1964 May 21 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Interfaith Council Dinner, 1962 November 27 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - International Executive Management Institute, 1963 August 19 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - International Federation for Modern Languages and Literature (9th International Congress), 1963 August 26-31 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - International Student Festival, 1960 April 7 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - International Student Festival, 1961 April 14 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - International Student Festival, 1962 March 23 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - International Student Festival, 1963 March 21 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - International Student Festival, 1964 February 27 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - International Student Festival, 1965 April 1-3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Italian Centennial at NYU, 1961 April 17 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Jackson, Thomas Jonathan "Stonewall," Hall of Fame Installation, 1957 May 19 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jacobs, Ralph R., Julius Ochs Adler Award awarded to, 1964 May 14 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Japan Society, Tea Ceremony, 1975 March 17 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Culture Foundation, 1962 December 9 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Tercentenary, 1955 February 24 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Tercentenary Convocation, 1955 April 3 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Kenan, William R., Jr., Lecture in History, 1970 March 12 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Kennedy, Mrs. John F., University Medal awarded to, 1962 October 17 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Kimball, Dr. and Mrs. Leroy, Dinner in honor of, 1956 May 22 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Kramer, Stanley, Citation, 1955 April 1 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Kristol, Irving, Lecture, 1970 April 15 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Kubitschek, Juscelino, Dinner for, Brazilian Institute, 1962 March 5 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Kwon, Dr. Joon-whi, University Medal awarded to, 1962 July (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Law, School of, Alumni Dinner, 1960 April 6 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Law, School of, Alumni Dinner, 1963 April 17 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Law, School of, Alumni Dinner, 1964 April 15 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Law, School of, Convocation, 1975 May 28 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Law, School of, Dean's Day, 1960 December 10 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Levinson, Harvey B. and Henry A., Julius Ochs Adler Award awarded to, 1961 May 11 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Loeb Student Center, Groundbreaking, 1957 October 17 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Loeb Student Center, Cornerstone Ceremony, 1958 December 10 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Loeb Student Center, Dedication of, 1959 November 24 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Loeb Student Center, Board of the Annual Awards Banquet, 1962 May 12 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Loew, Manus, Dormitory, Dedication of, 1955 October 8 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Lomax, Paul S., Business Education Center, Dedication of, 1973 May 5 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - McGhee, Dean Paul Ansley, Funeral, Eulogy given at, 1964 August 9 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Maas Essay Contest Awards, 1959 May 28 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Maas Essay Contest Awards, 1963 May 21 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Maas Essay Contest Awards, 1965 June 2 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Maison Francaise, Lunch and Dedication of, 1957 April 26 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Mathematics and Mechanics, Institute for, Symposium on Theory of Electromagnetic Waves, 1950 June 6-8 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mathematical Sciences, Institution of, Dedication of, 1954 November 29 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Mazer, Dr. Benjamin, Luncheon for, 1958 January 28 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Medallion Alumni, Dinner, 1962 May 16 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Medallion Alumni, Dinner, 1963 May 23 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Medallion Alumni, Dinner, 1975 May 29 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Medical Science Building, Dedication of: Folder #1, 1955 June 2 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Medical Science Building, Dedication of: Folder #2, 1955 June 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Medicine, School of, Address to Alumni, 1964 February 22 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health, Research Center for, Dedication of, 1965 March 15 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Merrill, Charles E., Hall, Dedication of, 1973 September 13 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mexican Dignitaries, Reception for, 1954 April 14 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Meyner, Hon. Robert B., Presentation of President's Citation to, 1958 March 19 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Mickiewicz, Adam, Lecture, 1955 December 6 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Morton, Rev. W. Scott, Installation of, as Executive Director of University Christian Foundation, 1963 September 30 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Moskowitz, Charles C., Dinner, 1973 March 21 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Moskowitz, Charles C., Lecture, 1973 March 21 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Moskowitz, Charles C., Dinner, 1974 March 20 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Moskowitz, Charles C., Lecture, 1974 March 20 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Nagle, Raymond J., 5th Anniversary as Dean of College of Dentistry, 1957 September 19 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Nelson, Provost Norton, Inauguration of: General Correspondence (1966 July 6 – October 14), 1966 October 6 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Nelson, Provost Norton, Inauguration of: Dinner, 1966 October 6 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Nelson, Provost Norton, Inauguration of: Invitees, List of, 1966 October 6 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Nelson, Provost Norton,Inauguration of: Press Releases, 1966 October 6 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Nelson, Provost Norton, Inauguration of: Printed material, 1966 October 6 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Nelson, Provost Norton, Inauguration of: Printed releases, 1966 October 6 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Newman, Jacob Louis, Citation awarded to, 1955 March 11 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Newsom, Carroll Vincent, Dinner in honor of, 1957 October 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Nichols, Charles Walter, Hall, Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1959 May 12 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Nichols, Charles Walter, Hall, Dedication of, 1960 January 27 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Niles, Chancellor Russell D., Reception for, 1964 February 3 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1955 November 22 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - PRSA Luncheon, 1955 February 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Pahlavi, Mohamed Reza Shaw, Shah of Iran, Honorary Degree awarded to, 1964 June 9 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Paik, Dr. L. George, University Medal awarded to, 1962 December 14 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Para-Educator Center for Young Adults, Dedication Ceremony, 1973 October 3 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Parents' Convocation, 1961 September 17 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Parents' Convocation, 1962 September 16 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Parents' Convocation, 1975 September 21 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Peace Corps, Trainees, Graduation, 1962 June 20 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Peace Corps Week, Kick-off, 1963 December 9 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Peixoto, Admiral Ernani do Admaral (Ambassador of Brazil), Luncheon for, 1957 March 21 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Perstare et Praestare, Induction of President James M. Hester as Honorary Member, 1963 February 26 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Phelps, Anson G., Lectures, 1955 February 23 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Phelps, Anson G., Lectures, 1962 February 28 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Phelps, Anson G., Lectures, 1964 February 26 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Phelps, Anson G., Lectures, 1969 November 5, 12, 18, 25 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, Installation, 1962 May 7 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Triennial Council, 1958 August 27-30 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, Institute of, Cornerstone Laying, 1950 May 24 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, Institute of, Benefit performance, Bolshoi Ballet, 1963 October 10 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Pinay, Antoine, University Medal awarded to, 1959 May 20 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Press (NYU), Reception, 1975 November 25 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Price, Phillip, Memorial Lounge (Loeb Student Center), Rededication of, 1974 March 6 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Psi Upsilon National Convention, 1962 September 7 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Executive Association Banquet, 1963 June 8 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Public Administration, Graduate School of, Executive Program for the City of New York and Metropolitan Area, 1962 June 13 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Puerto Rico, Alumni and University of Puerto Rico visit, 1962 December 4-8 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Puerto Rico, First Commencement Exercises (Includes photographs), 1969 December 6 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Correspondence (1970 January 20 - 1971 May 19), 1970 December 5 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Other material, 1970 December 5 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Photographs, 1970 December 5 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Printed material, 1970 December 5 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Publicity, 1970 December 5 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Correspondence (1970 December 10 - 1971 December 10), 1971 December 4 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Ceremony, 1971 December 4 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Photographs, 1971 December 4 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Printed material, 1971 December 4 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Puerto Rico Commencement Exercises: Publicity, 1971 December 4 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico Residence Center, Reception and Dinner, 1971 December 3 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Radhakrishnan, Savepalli (President of India), Honorary Degree awarded to: Folder #1, 1963 June 11 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Radhakrishnan, Savepalli (President of India), Honorary Degree awarded to: Folder #2, 1963 June 11 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Institute, Annual Dinner and Dance, 1971 January 19 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate Institute, Annual Dinner and Dance, 1972 February 17 (Box 29, Folder 4)